<?xml version="1.0" ?><the_root><conversation>my_convo_1<line id="0" speaker="player"><text>[start]</text><line id="1" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie! My sweet girl, you are safe! I was worried that the Almighty's followers had snatched you and taken you away from me forever.</text><script><triggerType>LE-convoLineCondition</triggerType><scriptName>HasJournalEntryAndValue</scriptName><parameter>Village</parameter><parameter>10</parameter></script><line id="2" speaker="player"><text>Father, I'm not a girl anymore. You don't have to worry because I've completed the rite of adulthood.</text><line id="3" speaker="npc"><text>I know you are no longer a child, Vasherie, but I must see the actual proof of your rite.</text><line id="4" speaker="player"><text>-give him the mushrooms-</text><line id="5" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie, these are not the correct mushrooms. These are unremarkable grey mushrooms found in the deep forest. The rite is incomplete, daughter. I am sorry but I cannot grant you adulthood.</text><line id="6" speaker="player"><text>The priestess said these were the right ones. She lied to me!</text><line id="7" speaker="npc"><text>That is a serious accusation about my most trusted priestess. As I said before, do you have any proof of her deception?</text><line id="8" speaker="player"><text>...No.</text><line id="9" speaker="npc"><text>Then you must be silent. Do not speak of this matter again. Ah, but I am glad that you are safe. You need to stay that way-- don't sneak outside the village walls. It may have been exciting before but now it is just dangerous. Run along now, Vasherie. I have a village to save.</text><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>SetJournalEntryValue</scriptName><parameter>Village</parameter><parameter>20</parameter></script><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>DestroyObject</scriptName><parameter>Preventer1</parameter></script></line></line><line id="10" speaker="player"><text>I must have picked the wrong mushrooms.</text><line id="11" speaker="npc"><text>You will get another chance, but right now I am just glad that you are safe. You need to stay that way-- don't sneak outside the village walls. It may have been exciting before but now it is just dangerous. Run along now, Vasherie. I have a village to save.</text><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>SetJournalEntryValue</scriptName><parameter>Village</parameter><parameter>20</parameter></script><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>DestroyObject</scriptName><parameter>Preventer1</parameter></script></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line><line id="12" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie, the followers are coming. I don't have time for your problems. Any other time but now I would gladly help you. I have the lives of our people resting in my hands.</text><script><triggerType>LE-convoLineCondition</triggerType><scriptName>NotHasJournalEntryAndValue</scriptName><parameter>Village</parameter><parameter>10</parameter></script></line></line></conversation></the_root>