<?xml version="1.0" ?><the_root><conversation>my_convo_1<line id="0" speaker="player"><text>[start]</text><line id="1" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie! You're alive. Thank the Almighty. I sent warriors out to find you, despite the fact that they were outmatched. How did you survive?</text><line id="2" speaker="player"><text>Thank the Almighty that I survived. *Tell your father what happened*</text><line id="3" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie, I am glad that the Almighty was able to guide you through your ordeal. You have proven yourself to be considered an adult member of the tribe, and to someday soon take up the role of Shaman.</text><line id="6" speaker="player"><text>-Continue-</text><line id="8" speaker="npc"><text>By destroying Regulus you have ensured the safety of the Almighty.</text></line></line><line id="7" speaker="player"><text>-Continue-</text><line id="12" speaker="npc"><text>By disabling Regulus, you have ensured the safety of the Almighty, for a time. Maybe one day he will awaken and serve the Almighty as he was meant to.</text></line></line></line></line><line id="4" speaker="player"><text>I think you and I both know the truth about &quot;The Almighty&quot;  * Tell your father what happened*</text><line id="5" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie... it is very important that you do not tell anyone what happened last night. The villagers feel safe knowing that the Almighty is watching over them. You do not want to disrupt that balance by telling them the truth. Regardless, you have proven yourself to be considered an adult member of the tribe, and to someday soon take up the role of Shaman.</text><line id="9" speaker="player"><text>-Continue-</text><line id="11" speaker="npc"><text>By destroying Regulus you have ensured the safety of Gottheit.</text></line></line><line id="10" speaker="player"><text>-Continue-</text><line id="13" speaker="npc"><text>By disabling Regulus, you have ensured the safety of Gottheit, for a time. Maybe one day he will awaken and serve Gottheit as he was meant to.</text></line></line></line></line></line></line></conversation></the_root>