<?xml version="1.0" ?><the_root><conversation>my_convo_1<line id="0" speaker="player"><text>[start]</text><line id="1" speaker="npc"><text>(whirring of machines)</text><line id="2" speaker="player"><text>Almighty?</text><line id="3" speaker="npc"><text>You are one of them. You are one of my people.</text><line id="4" speaker="player"><text>What are you?</text><line id="5" speaker="npc"><text>You are correct to be curious. I am, wait, you remind me of another, someone who came here when he was very young. What is your name?</text><line id="6" speaker="player"><text>Vasherie</text><line id="7" speaker="npc"><text>Then you are his daughter. Your father spoke those words  What are you? to me. I told him my story, like I told it to  every shaman before him. They knew the truth about me and my past, yet they lied to their people. Are you here to be the next shaman? Answer quickly for we do not have much time.</text><line id="8" speaker="player"><text>No, I am here to save my people.</text><line id="9" speaker="npc"><text>So you must know the truth about me and Regulus. We have time before my metal servants break the outer walls of the spaceship. Let me explain</text><line id="10" speaker="player"><text>Go on</text><line id="11" speaker="npc"><text>I was born with one purpose: destroy the Sinistra. They lived very, very far away on a distant planet. I was created to destroy them. My creators were a people who treasured me. One woman even happened to scrawl a name, GOTTHEIT on my name plate.</text><line id="12" speaker="player"><text>(Silent in awe)</text><line id="13" speaker="npc"><text>On our journey to destroy the Sinistra, my spaceship crashed brutally into this harsh planet that you call home. All of my people withered and died from sickness and hunger, and all I had left were my mechanical servants. I could not save my crew.</text><line id="14" speaker="player"><text>Thats awful.</text><line id="15" speaker="npc"><text> Centuries passed. I had this yearning building inside of me to kill, you see, for that was my sole purpose. It still is my reason for existence.</text><line id="16" speaker="player"><text>Who are The Sinistra?</text><line id="17" speaker="npc"><text>Automated response (different voice) They are the enemy. Your directive is to destroy their planet in quadrant 5  8  21. I do not know. I only know that they are there and that our location is very far from their homeworld.</text><line id="18" speaker="player"><text>How do you survive with that directive if you cannot fight your enemy?</text><line id="19" speaker="npc"><text> Like a virus it spread deep down inside of me to all of my basic functions. I could feel it writhing, corrupting my systems. With enough time, the corruption spread to my lead robot Regulus. He was a normal probe, but one day he started questioning the objective to destroy but he talked as if he were not aware that he was questioning our most basic orders. He became the anomaly, the tumor.</text><line id="20" speaker="player"><text>What did you do?</text><line id="21" speaker="npc"><text>I sent him to a cliff, hoping that he would fall to his destruction. I could not allow his heresy to spread to the other probes. He became something terrible.</text><line id="22" speaker="player"><text>Go on.</text><line id="23" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie, my yearning to kill has gone away because it resides within him. He no longer questions it, he follows it blindly with no thought as to who he is killing. It will, however, be restored if Regulus is able to interface with my AI core.</text><line id="24" speaker="player"><text>If I destroy him, will your directive disappear?</text><line id="25" speaker="npc"><text>I do not know. Regulus is coming. I can feel him. Now you know why Im here, Vasherie. It is time to prove yourself. Save me, to save your people. You need to repair the three probe control consoles found throughout the ship. This will allow me to disable the probes so that they do not destroy your people. </text><line id="26" speaker="player"><text>What do I need to do to save my people?</text><line id="27" speaker="npc"><text>Save me to save your people. I may not be God, but I have protected your people for many generations. You need to repair the three probe control consoles found throughout the ship. This will allow me to disable the probes so that they do not destroy your people.</text><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>OpenJournalEntry</scriptName><parameter>Ship</parameter></script><script><triggerType>LE-trigger-noCondition</triggerType><scriptName>SetJournalEntryValue</scriptName><parameter>Ship</parameter><parameter>20</parameter><parameter></parameter><parameter></parameter></script></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line><line id="28" speaker="npc"><text>Save me to save your people. I may not be God, but I have protected your people for many generations. You need to repair the three probe control consoles found throughout the ship. This will allow me to disable the probes so that they do not destroy your people.</text><script><triggerType>LE-convoLineCondition</triggerType><scriptName>HasJournalEntryAndValue</scriptName><parameter>Ship</parameter><parameter>20</parameter></script></line></line></conversation></the_root>