<?xml version="1.0" ?><the_root><conversation>my_convo_1<line id="0" speaker="player"><text>[start]</text><line id="1" speaker="npc"><text>Vasherie, I heard that your rite was not completed. It is a shame. I believe that you have proven yourself ready to be an adult.</text><line id="2" speaker="player"><text>Thank you, Sir.</text><line id="3" speaker="npc"><text>You are welcome.</text><line id="4" speaker="player"><text>Sir, why are the metal defying the will of the Almighty?</text><line id="5" speaker="npc"><text>You do remember the origin story of the Almighty, yes?</text><line id="6" speaker="player"><text>Yes, however I don't want to hear it again.</text><line id="7" speaker="npc"><text>The followers have cast themselves from the Almighty and seek only to hurt us. They are gathering their cursed troops and seek to annihilate our people and even the Almighty herself. We do not know the reason for their crusade. Your father is sending warriors to gain intelligence on the problem. I will tell you a secret. Your father does not want anyone to worry, but they are coming for us. Our village does not have much time left.</text><line id="8" speaker="player"><text>When will he tell the village?</text><line id="9" speaker="npc"><text>Soon.</text><line id="10" speaker="player"><text>What will we do?</text><line id="11" speaker="npc"><text>He will inform the village and send the warriors out to confront the problem. </text></line></line></line></line></line></line><line id="14" speaker="player"><text>No, tell me about the story of our tribe, please.</text><line id="15" speaker="npc"><text>A grand being tore through the sky and fell upon our land. It talked to the One of our people and only to the One. The One became a shaman and spread the knowledge of the Almighty. Our way of life grew better over generations and soon the Almighty's influence was felt all over our land. Her followers, the beings that rose from the Almighty, were always steadfast and docile until yesterday. </text><line id="16" speaker="player"><text></text><line id="17" speaker="npc"><text>The followers have cast themselves from the Almighty and seek only to hurt us. They are gathering their cursed troops and seek to annihilate our people and even the Almighty herself. We do not know the reason for their crusade. Your father is sending warriors to gain intelligence on the problem. I will tell you a secret. Your father does not want anyone to worry, but they are coming for us. Our village does not have much time left.</text><line id="18" speaker="player"><text>When will he tell the village?</text><line id="19" speaker="npc"><text>Soon.</text><line id="20" speaker="player"><text>What will we do?</text><line id="21" speaker="npc"><text>He will inform the village and send the warriors out to confront the problem. </text></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></line></conversation></the_root>